A Guide to the Stuart-Baldwin Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #10278-a
Stuart-Balwin Papers 1859-1926
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
10378-a
15 items
Mrs. A. S. Robertson, Jr.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This addition was a gift to the Library from Mrs A. S. Robertson, Jr., of Orange, Virginia, on December 5, 1983.
Scope and Content
This accession consists of 15 items, 1850-1926, business and legal papers pertaining to the Stuart, Baldwin, and Robertson families. Included are stock certificates, bonds, a letter, a copy of John T. Farish's will together with copies of court decisions concerning a trust fund established by the will, and two printed book reviews of Alexander Hugh Holmes Stuart. 1807-1891 by Alexander F. Robertson.
Container List
- Miscellaneous
  - Stock certificate of the Central Bank of Virginia, issued to Miss Mary J. Baldwin, 1859 Jan. 20
  - Bonds, William H. Harris to Benjamin T. Bagby, paid by Chesley Bolling, Oct. 22, 1877, 1873 Oct. 1; (4 items)
  - First Mortgage Bond of the Rockbridge Alum Springs Company, 1880 Oct. 1
  - Hunter McGuire to [Alexander H.H.] Stuart re borrowing money, w/ reply at bottom signed by Alex. H.H. Stuart, 1890 May 10; ALS,
  - Will of John T. Farish, 1890 Dec. 8; (copy)
  - Stock certificate of the Staunton Perpetual Building and Loan Company, 1893 May 25
  - Stock certificate of the Staunton Perpetual Building and Loan Company, 1893 July 18
  - Appeal, Alexander F. Robertson et. al., as Trustees, Respondents, v. Martha G. de Brulatour et. al., Apellants, post 1907 Apr. 16
  - Report of Referee' Alexander F. Robertson, as sole surviving trustee of a trust created under the last will of John T. Farish, deceased, Plaintiff, against Thomas H. Somerville et. al., Defendants, New York Supreme Court, New York County, 1908 May 14
  - Book review from Virginia Law Register of Robertson, Alexander F. Alexander Hugh Holmes Stuart. 1807-1891. (Richmond: William Byrd Press, 1925.)
  - University of Virginia Alumni News, Vol. XIV, No. 10, w/ review of Robertson, Alexander F. Alexander Hugh Holmes Stuart. 1807-1891. (Richmond: William Byrd Press, 1925.), 1926 June-July
  - Stock certificate of the Bank of the Valley in Virginia, issued to Alexander H.H. Stuart